the first task of this problem
is to prompt the user for some input
we can print this prompt to the screen
calling the
put s method
[Music]
so we've got our prompt type anything
you want
and we're passing it as an argument to
the put s method
you won't usually see parentheses used
with put s
but we could put our argument in
parentheses and
the code would work just the same
[Music]
so let's print our prompt to the screen
and it's printing appropriately so now
we can look at the next step of our
problem
we need to allow for the user to give
some input to our program
now you'll notice that if we just run
our program as it is
it prints out the prompt and completes
execution
the program is not going to wait for the
user to input anything
[Music]
in order to change that we can use the
get s
method you can think of that as get
string
and this will cause program execution to
pause
and wait for user input
so let's see what that looks like
so we've been prompted to type anything
we want
and now the program is waiting
i'll input hello and when i press
enter or return our program will
continue executing
[Music]
and in this instance our program doesn't
do anything else so it ends
[Music]
so now that we are waiting for and
obtaining that user input
we need to find a way to display that
input back to the user
when getting input from a user it's a
good idea to store that user input in a
variable
so that you can pass it around or use it
later
in this case we can use the local
variable text
to store the user input
just like we called put s and pass the
string in as an argument
we can also pass our local variable text
in as an argument
and our program will output the value of
text as a string
so let's run our program again
[Music]
we've been prompted for our input and
again i'm going to input hello
when i press enter hello is printed
right back
out to me and the program ends
you